<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on Anna Quaglieri</title>
    <link>/tags/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on Anna Quaglieri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bioconductor Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>/community/coc_bioc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/community/coc_bioc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Since December 2021 I&amp;rsquo;m part of the Bioconductor Code of Conduct (CoC). Incidents happening at every Bioconductor conferences can be reported and the committee is responsible to file them and lead to a conflict resolution which will depend on the gravity of the incident.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R-Ladies Melbourne</title>
      <link>/community/rladies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/community/rladies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The group, founded in 2016, is the first R Programming community for women and
supporters in Australia. I was the main organiser of the group in 2017/2018 where we organised 12
events (workshops, seminars and networking nights). During that period we also defined the
structure to become a not-for-profit association; provided funding for women to attend the
useR! conference; gained a new sponsor, Nous Group, and renewed sponsorship from CSL.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I summarized the R-Ladies achievement during that period in a blog post &lt;a href=&#34;https://rladiesmelb2018.netlify.com/&#34;&gt;https://rladiesmelb2018.netlify.com/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkville Toastmasters</title>
      <link>/community/toastmasters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/community/toastmasters/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I joined the group in 2019 and since then I&amp;rsquo;ve been learning so much about giving presentations and growing my confidence in front of an audience. The community at Toastmasters Parkville is extremely supportive and engaging making every event night super fun!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>


