<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Community initiatives on Anna Quaglieri</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Community initiatives on Anna Quaglieri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FeMS mentoring</title>
      <link>/project/fems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/fems/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In June 2021, I joined Mass Dynamics and at the same time the field of Mass Spectrometry (MS), a completely new field for me. From the experience of being part of the R-Ladies Melbourne and Global community I realised how important it has been to be part of a community. Thereofe, I looked for a MS community and FeMS was there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I took part into their yearly mentoring program between December 2021 until June 2022. During that period i was assigned to a mentoring group, comprising of 2 mentors and a few mentees, all working in different areas of MS in the Australian and Asian time zones. We met monthly and each month we would discuss a different topic, from personal development, MS intruments and new techologies. I now feel way more part of the MS community and I have people that I can contact for suggestions and support!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bioconductor Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>/project/coc_bioc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/coc_bioc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Since December 2021 I&amp;rsquo;m part of the Bioconductor Code of Conduct (CoC). Incidents happening at every Bioconductor conferences can be reported and the committee is responsible to file them and lead to a conflict resolution which will depend on the gravity of the incident.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R-Ladies Melbourne</title>
      <link>/project/rladies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/rladies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The group, founded in 2016, is the first R Programming community for women and
supporters in Australia. I was the main organiser of the group in 2017/2018 where we organised 12
events (workshops, seminars and networking nights). During that period we also defined the
structure to become a not-for-profit association; provided funding for women to attend the
useR! conference; gained a new sponsor, Nous Group, and renewed sponsorship from CSL.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I summarized the R-Ladies achievement during that period in a blog post &lt;a href=&#34;https://rladiesmelb2018.netlify.com/&#34;&gt;https://rladiesmelb2018.netlify.com/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkville Toastmasters</title>
      <link>/project/toastmasters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/toastmasters/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I joined the group in 2019 and since then I&amp;rsquo;ve been learning so much about giving presentations and growing my confidence in front of an audience. The community at Toastmasters Parkville is extremely supportive and engaging making every event night super fun!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>


